In this video, you will learn how to guide shoppers to sub-pages in your brand store that match
their interests with sponsored brands' product collection and video format.
Your brand store is more than a landing page.
It's a place to inspire shoppers and showcase your product line.
Let's start by building a sponsored brands' campaign and linking it to a specific sub-page in your
store.
Step 1.
Choose product collection or video format and select your target store sub-page, like cappuccino
collection.
Step 2.
For videos, spotlight flagship products that are easily found at the top of a sub-page.
For collections, use lifestyle imagery that brings your products to life, leveraging AI to help
create high-quality images easily.
Step 3.
Write a headline that highlights the benefit of your products to communicate value to potential
customers.
Step 4.
Choose three products from your sub-page that reflect the theme.
Try using top performers with strong ratings to maximize impact.
Step 5.
When using keyword targeting, use category terms, feature-specific terms, and branded terms to reach
high-intent shoppers.
For product targeting, select items that are similar to your featured products or aligned with the
category and interests related to your sub-page.
Create separate ad groups or campaigns for each targeting strategy for better control.
Step 6.
Design your brand store sub-page to convert by featuring advertised products prominently at the
top of the page.
Incorporate rich visuals or demonstration videos and consider the opportunity to cross-sell by adding
deep links to related categories.
Linking your ads to specific sub-pages of your store works especially well when promoting specific
products within a category,
launching a new line or targeting high-intent shoppers on a given category.
This approach is also useful when optimizing your store's performance.
Use your brand store insights to identify opportunities.
Check the pages tab to see which sub-pages drive sales and which need more visibility.
You can then adjust your campaigns to direct more shoppers to underperforming pages or capitalize
on your top performing pages.
Put learning into practice.
Create a sponsored brands campaign driving to a sub-page.
Watch our other two videos in this series to learn more ways to connect sponsored brands to your
brand store.